bigbadtoystore.com 2019-11-04

# Privacy Policy

  1. BBTS Help Center
  2. Privacy Policy

#### **Table of Contents:**

  * Our Commitment to Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment to Data Security
  * Our Commitment to Children's Privacy
  * How to access or Correct Your Information
  * How to Contact Us

#### **Our Commitment to Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

#### **The Information we Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the BigBadToyStore website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Payment Information

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Phone Number

#### **The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website to open an account or receive our newsletter. There is an easily identifiable link at the bottom of every newsletter that you can use to opt-out. The operation of our website requires the use of cookies. The data contained in these cookies does not contain any personal information. Cookies are removed at the end of your session. We use Google Analytics to better serve our customers. Google does not use or record your personal information in any way. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.

#### **Our Commitment to Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. At no point do we store complete credit card information on our servers.

#### **Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

#### **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access and update all your personally identifiable information that we collect by accessing the "my account" portion of the BigBadToyStore website. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

#### **How to Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [ service@bigbadtoystore.com](mailto:service@bigbadtoystore.com).
